ah..
嗯..
Good morning
早安
嗯..
Hibiki
响
嗯.嗯..
Today's a great day as usual2
今天也精神满满
嗯.嗯..
right
真不错呢
Nope
才不呢
Hey!?
哎!?
There's a quiz today
今天有小考测验
So
所以
I was trying to study yesterday
昨天想着要好好复习的
Results of
结果
I fell asleep!
就那么睡着了!
If you have kept a proper sleeping schedule
若平常就勤快复习的话
Well do not you do not need a headache
不就用不着头疼了嘛
Hibiki..
响..
Okay
OK
I know
我明白了
You can lecture me
妳那番话
I listen to the next some other time
我下次再听
Did you study, Ellen?
艾莲昨天复习了吗?
Yes
嗯
I did
万无一失喔
Really
真的吗
Oh no
糟糕
What should I do?
该怎么办呢?
Oh yeah!
对了!
"Healing Chest!"
"治愈音樂盒!"
What are you doing with that?
妳拿它要做什么?
When we got this
我们得到它的时候
Remember what she told us
不是被提醒过吗
The Healing Chest
治愈音樂盒
has a lot of other powers
还蕴藏着许多神秘的力量
So
所以
maybe also
说不定也有
it can help me on my quiz
用于应付考试的力量
ah...
啊...
Nope!
不行!
You use it like that
用在这种地方
Can not!
可不行!
Yeah Meow!
就是呀喵!
Then
那么
how can we use it?
它要用来做什么的?
Hey!?
哎!?
In fact is
其实是
a piggy bank?
存钱筒之类的?
There's no for you coins
没有能把硬币
place to insert, Meow
放进去的地方喵
Then
那么
a jewelry box
是宝石盒
In a sense
从某种意义上说
Looks like it
它看上去确实很像
but that's probably not it, Meow
但应该不是喵
Well oh
嗯嘛
Oh, overall
嘛 总之
please just help me
请帮我
on the quiz
这次的考试
security through the, okay
安全度过吧
ah!
啊!
Hey
真是的
Hibiki
响
Crescendo Tone
克雷仙多音调
What? What?
什么?什么?
This kind of study yourself thing
这种事情
you should work hard
要靠妳自己去努力
Hey
喂
ah..
嗯..
Healing Chest
治愈音樂盒
La? la? la? la? la?
Ra? Ra? Ra? Ra? Ra?
啦?啦?啦?啦?啦?
Suite Suite Precure?
组曲 组曲 光之美少女?
Suite Precure?
组曲 光之美少女?
Suite Suite Precure?
组曲 组曲 光之美少女?
Suite Precure?
组曲 光之美少女?
We're family because we care for each other
Sasa eaeba FAMILY
相互扶持 就是家庭
Filling each and every page with love
Ai afu reru DIARY
满溢着爱的 日记
If we all combine our strengths
Hitori hitori ga chikara awasete
每个人的力量 联合起来
We can bring forth a brand new day
Tsunaide yuku BRAND NEW DAY
连结起   崭新的  一天
We can press on one step at a time
Ippo zutsu demo susumou
一步一步也要向前进
（Go! Go!）
We'll form a circle, standing hand in hand
Te ni te ni totte wa ni natte
手牵着手围成圈（跳跃 ! ）
（Jump ! ）
So let's stand up and face our futures!
Mirai he mukatte Stand Up!
朝着未来 站起来!（光之美少女 ! ）
（Precure ! ）
And make our hearts one
Kimochi wo hitotsu ni shite
让我们同心协力
Sing !  I want us to stand together
Sing !  Ima minna de
歌唱吧 !  现在 大家一起
Swing !  And sing our hearts out
Swing !  Utaitai
摇摆吧 !  我想要唱
For you
为了妳（为了我）
(for me)
For girls
为了女孩（为了男孩）
(for boys)
Until we wipe our tears away
Sono namida kawaku made
直到 那眼泪干枯
Dream!  Having weathered the storm
Dream!  Ame wo koeta
梦想!  越过了风雨
Believe !  The power of our beating hearts
Believe !  Genki na kokoro
相信 !  朝气蓬勃的心
Is unlimited∞ Our smiles will always be number one!
Mugendai∞ itsudemo egao ga number one!
无限大∞  笑脸永远是  最棒的!
Suite Suite Precure?
组曲 组曲 光之美少女?
ah..
嗯..
英文翻译: Ladholyman
Timer/QC/Encoder、OP、ED: Maceart Magenta
英文字幕提供:Doremi-fansubs、CureCom
网址:www.doremi-fansubs.com
www.curecom.net
时间轴、BT发布、压制:Tommy 角川浩良
网页翻译:小雷 帝台春(校订)
主剧情、预告翻译:svizzera
文稿校对:雪柳
字幕网盘发布:asdfe0
新OP、ED歌词翻译:koyami
歌词校对:雪柳、圣域字幕组 修饰
ah...
嗯...
Hibiki
响
It's upside down
书拿反了
It's no good..
不行了..
I don't know this at all
完全看不懂
请下载影片后24小时内删除
若个人私自散布传播造成相关问题 Curefans小队概不负责
新OP、ED歌词采用英中日字幕(以加强翻译日文语气)
本字幕仅供个人试看使用 若你喜欢本小队作品 请支持购买正版
唉
I knew it
也是呢
ah..
嗯..
想看光之美少女系列动漫请上prcsub.17heha.com
中文字幕制作: Curefans小队
ah!!
啊!!
Oh yeah
对了
本小队CureFans急需Suite光之美少女动画中文翻译2名  有意愿报名请MAIL至asdfe0@qq.com 应征
Hibiki
响
did you call me?
叫我吗?
I did, I did
是的 是的
Nishijima?
西岛?
How did she know
只听那口哨声就知道了
Waon
和音
you always mention it
妳一直都挂在嘴边的
when I'm in trouble,
我感到困扰的时候
you said you'd help me, right
说会帮我的吧
Eh, What
哎 什么
I need the power of the moment
需要我的力量的时刻
you finally arrived
终于到来了
need my help arrived?
到来了吗?
Yes, yes
是的 是的
Okay
OK
leave it to me
交给我吧
That's how it is
事情就是这样
I see
原来如此
Ah
啊
Naito classmate
内藤同学
Account of your seat
占了妳的座位
sorry for taking
真是对不起呢
That's fine
不 这没什么
Then
那么
how about this?
这个故事如何?
Last night..
昨晚..
I was jogging in the neighborhood
我在附近的公园慢跑
and
就在
while I was taking a break
中途休息的时候
Wang~
汪~
ah
啊
Wang~
汪~
Wang
汪
"Wang~" This
"汪~"这样
I heard these dogs bark
狗吠的声音听上去
like it was a symphony
就像是音乐一般
Amazing, right
很不可思议吧
Wow
哎
how interesting
真有趣
Nishijima
西岛
啊
so this story
这个故事
what does that have to do with the quiz?
和考试有什么关系呢?
Nothing
完全没关系喔
Nothing!!
没有关系吗!!
Although
虽然
I couldn't help you with your quiz
对考试没帮助
But I would like to at least take this story to Hibiki
但我想让响能不能藉此故事
I can cheer you up
打起精神来
Well
那个
I wanted you to help me
不是说要帮我
with through the quiz difficulties
度过考试难关吗
ah
嗯
ah!!
啊!!
This is
这是
your last test
上一次的考卷
What a score
好厉害的成绩
Jeez
真是的
Hibiki also really the
响也真是的
I am in studying, too
我在学习方面
won't lose to Hibiki, too
也有不输给响的自信喔
You know extent, from the bad
从糟糕的程度上来说
Ah
啊
I see Is all about
是这么一回事啊
Is the case
就是如此
Jeez
真是的
Hibiki, you're so foolish
响也真是神经大条
Ah
嗯
Sorry about that
对不起
Later
那么
I'm leaving
我告辞了
What a refreshing
真是行事直爽啊
What about
为什么
she carrying the tests running around
她拿着考卷到处跑呢
Ah
啊
Results of
结果
I didn't get anything done in the end
什么都没做成啊
脚本：成田良美  演出：田中裕太
作画：上野ケン    美术：戸杉奈津子
Waon! The Mysteries of the Healing Chest Meow!
不可思议的治愈音樂盒喵!
30话 哇哦!
What
什么
Healing Chest
你是说治愈音樂盒
Yes
是的
It's a box about this big
她们拿着像这么大的盒子
A box that big?
你说像这么大的盒子?
You idiot!
笨蛋!
You want to say that box
你想说那盒子
retrieved it from the Evil Forest
从魔响之森回来了吗
This is just me muttering..
虽说如此..
But is that place really that scary?
那里真有那么可怕吗?
You idiot!
笨蛋!
Are you doubting me?
你是在质疑本大人的话吗?
The adults had the evil of that forest
本大人曾经在魔响之森中
I had quite the frightening experience
遭遇了前所未有的危机
Uh..
那个..
What happened, exactly?
到底发生了什么?
ah
嗯
Well..
那是..
What was it?
什么来着?
Mephisto adult!
梅菲斯特大人!
This will enable us to
这会让我们
well more curious than
更好奇不是嘛
Please tell us
请告诉我们呀
Shut up, Shut up!
闭嘴 闭嘴!
Overall
总之
before things get dicey
在事情变得棘手之前
steal the Healing Chest!
把治愈音樂盒给我抢过来!
Got it
听懂了吗
That's weird
真奇怪
Clearly met
明明碰到了
it was truly frightening
很大的危机
but why can't I remember
但什么都想不起来
Why?
为什么?
Hibiki's test
响的考试
How did go, Meow
怎么样了喵
I haven't even asked , Meow..
似乎不用问了喵..
oh
唉
It's over for me
我真是糟糕
You're overreacting
别这么夸张嘛
How was it for you two?
妳们俩考得怎么样?
Uh..
呃..
Well..
这个嘛..
This is Kanade's test, Meow
这是奏的考卷喵
ah
啊
Stop that
快住手
That test such a formidable results
这么厉害的成绩
for me
对我来说
is too amazing
实在是太耀眼了
ah
啊
This is Siren's test, Meow
这是赛莲的考卷喵
S..Stop
住..住手
Stop
住手
It's okay
没关系的
This isn't the only test
考试又不是只有这一次
Yes
是啊
We still have midterms and finals
有期中和期末考
there are proficiency tests, too
其他还有实力测验
Other
另外
next year we have entrance exams, too..
明年终于轮到升学考..
Ah brawl
啊哗哗
哗哗
H..Hey
那..那个
Ellen
艾莲
I'm s..sorry
对..对不起
啊哗
Well
嘛
Overall
总之
we have PE next
下节是体育课
so cheer up
转换下心情吧
Yeah
嗯
that's right
也是呢
Oh
哦
Meow
喵
Ha
哈
Ha ha
哈哈
Ha
哈
ah
嗯
Hee hee
嘻嘻
shout
喝
Bounce
蹦
Wow ah
哇啊
But
但是
what's going on?
这是怎么回事啊?
Ah
啊
I see
原来如此
the Fairy Tones
音调精灵们
are cheering me up
是想让我恢复精神
everyone
大家
Thank you very much
谢谢你们了
everyone
大家
Good job
真厉害呢
What Dodo
什么厉害呢 Dodo
Hey
哎
It wasn't you guys?
这不是你们做的吗?
We don't know, Rere
不知道呀 Rere
Hey!
哎!
It's a normal flight of stairs
是普通的阶梯对吧
Okay
那么
Time for PE to refuel
体育课要加油啰
Hibiki looks happier
响似乎精神好些了呢
Well
嘛
Because PE is Hibiki
因为体育是响
the only best class
唯一擅长的科目啊
Ah la?
啊勒?
Yes
是的
other than PE
除了体育之外
I can't do anything
我什么都不行
Hum
哼哼
ah
啊
Hey
那个
Kanade
奏
I'm sorry
对不起
Well, everyone
好了
Line up!
列队!
W..What's going on?
怎 怎么了?
Jeez
真是的
What's with that?
那是什么呀?
Another sound..
声音又变了..
ah
嗯
ah..
嗯..
Hibiki
响
ah
啊
Here to you
给妳
Hey
哎
I'm fine
不用了
Don't feel shy
别跟我客气
Okay
吃吧
Kanade..
奏..
Ah~sip
啊~呷
Thanks
谢谢
I'm feeling better now, maybe
我好像比较有精神了
We're hungry, too, Dodo
我们也肚子饿了 Dodo
Oh
哦
What should we do
要怎么做才好呢
The Healing Chest
治愈音樂盒
hope you are able to use, Rere
希望妳们能使用 Rere
But
但是
we don't know how to use it yet
我们还不知道使用方法呢
Don't worry
没问题的
I always feel
我总觉得
like this will work
一定能成功使用的
Hey
哎
The Healing Chest
治愈音樂盒
"Feel" to open
用"感觉"去开启
Oh
啊
ah
嗯
I see
也是呢
Then
那么
have a go at it, Ellen
就拜托艾莲了
Feel it..
用感觉去开启..
You don't have to say it twice
不用讲二遍啦
Fairy Tones
音调精灵们
Return to me
请到我的身边
Dodo
Rere
Mimi
Fafa
Soso
Lala
Sisi
poof meow
喵噗
Thank you, Dodo
谢谢 Dodo
Looks like it went well
好像是成功了呢
But
但是
today sure was weird
今天还真是奇怪呢
Eh
咦
The Fairy Tones didn't do that?
那不是音调精灵们做的?
We don't know anything, Fafa
不是我们做的 Fafa
Hey
哎
Then..
那么..
It's truly weird
真是不可思议啊
Ah meow
啊喵
I haven't said anything, Meow
我什么都还没说呢喵
ah...
啊...
That means..
那么说的话..
Hibiki sister
响姐姐
how did your test go?
考试如何啦?
Why
怎样
whatever!
都无所谓啦!
Sounds you like
看妳的样子
sure and original the normal, right
肯定和原先一样吧
You screwed up, didn't you!
总之是没考好吧!
Were you say of
被你说中了
I knew it
果然
Also
也是
It's your own fault
自作自受
Leave me alone!
别管我啦!
ah
嗯
I'll do that
我会这么做的
eh!!
啊!!
eh
啊
W.W..What?
什.什..什么?
eh
啊
Ha ha
哈哈
Interesting
真有趣
Why
什么啊
What's going on?
怎么回事?
Ha ha
哈哈
So weird
真奇怪
Hey
喂
Ako
亚子
Wait I look at
等我一下啦
Oh ha ha
呵呵哈哈
Ha ha ha
哈哈哈
Oh oh oh
呵呵呵
Ah ha
嗯哼
But
但是
another sound..
声音又一次..
Sound?
声音?
Oh yeah!
对了
Otokichi
音吉先生
Maybe let's will know what to ask
说不定会知道些什么的
What a beautiful performance
真是美妙的演奏
I'm sure it's Otokichi
一定是音吉先生
Ah la?
啊勒?
There's no one there
明明没人
The organ's playing itself..
管风琴却自己动了..
ah~
啊~
Ellen
艾莲
Calm down
冷静下来
It's fine
没关系的
I think
应该
Yes meow
是呀喵
That it can't be quiet
不能安静一点吗
Rare to have such a wonderful the performance
难得有如此美妙的演奏
you can't hear otherwise
都听不到了唷
Otokichi!
音吉先生!
Otokichi
音吉先生
O..Organ's playing itself
管..管风琴它自己动了
Ellen
艾莲
calm down
冷静点
ah
嗯
Seems
大概是
like the fairy, the source of all sounds
作为声音起源的精灵
came close to it is near
来到了附近吧
hey
哎
Which means..
那么说..
This is your doing, isn't it
这是妳的力量没错吧
Crescendo Tone
克雷仙多音调
hey
哎
H..How
为..为何
do you know that name?
你知道这名字?
ah
啊
You seem
看上去
The spirit of well
精神不错呢
Otokichi
音吉
Long time no see
好久不见
Crescendo Tone
克雷仙多音调
Yeah hey!?
耶哎!?
hey
哎
hey!!
哎!!
本字幕情节为正式发布OX版本 重点标题文都有注记英中
?
Fans
小队
?
Cure
后半段开始放送
Just a little while longer, right
就差一点了呢
Yes
是的
Will we make it?
来得及吗?
I'll make sure we do
我会让它来得及的
Definitely
一定
Uh that
那个
When you talk de qijin interrupting
聊得起劲时打断你们
I am sorry
真不好意思
What is the relationship between you two?
你们俩是什么关系呢?
Well..
这个..
You'll know later
到时自然会告诉妳们
ah..
嗯..
Otokichi is quite..
音吉先生真是..
mysterious, Meow
神秘呢喵
Yes, yes
嗯 嗯
You also think so, really
你们也这么觉得
So having said that
话说回来
means today were due
该不会今天
those incredible the sounds
那些不可思议的声音
All because
都是因为
to Crescendo Tone's power
克雷仙多音调的力量
It happened?
才发生的?
Yes
是的
Even
该不会连
the dogs "Wang" wonderful sound
"汪"奇妙的声音
also because you?
也是因为妳?
Yes
是的
Why are you doing that?
为何要这么做呢?
I wanted to cheer Hibiki on
我想要为响加油
I thought the fun sounds
我本来想试用有趣的声音
汪
can give her energy
让她打起精神好好复习
汪
Wang~wang~wang
汪~汪~汪
But Hibiki
但是响她
fell asleep, Meow
睡得死死的呢喵
Shut up, you..
真多嘴..
But
但是
why
为什么
why do it for me?
要为了我这么做呢?
I want to cheer on the people that are down
沮丧的人们加油打气
我想要为
Only
仅仅
that's all
如此而已
Ah~wah wah
啊~哇哇
哇哇
Behaved, behaved
乖 乖
哇哇
What's wrong?
到底是怎么了呀?
Ah
啊
Ah~ha ha
啊~哈哈
Ah~
啊~
Catch it properly!
好好接住球啊!
You too
你才是
Where are you throwing the ball
在往哪儿扔球啊
Ah
嗯
Ye
耶
W..What
怎..怎么了
Ye
耶
Ha ha
哈哈
What's going on
这是怎么了
Wow
哇
It's so weird
真奇怪
This is interesting
真有趣
Ah ha ha..
啊哈哈..
Really is amazing
真是强大呢
The power of sounds
声音的力量
Everyone
大家
I am so sorry
真是对不起
ah!?
嗯!?
You've been cheering me on
妳们这么努力鼓励我
but I've been feeling down
而我却一直这么消沉
The next test
下一次考试
I definitely will do my best
绝对会努力的
Thanks
谢谢妳
Crescendo Tone
克雷仙多音调
She fell asleep again
又睡着了
Ah
啊
A Note, Meow!
音符喵!
We harmonized, Meow
我们合声了喵
Trio the Minor
小调岛三重唱
Today to let you'll be
今天就要让妳们
taking that Healing Chest
把治愈音樂盒给交出来
What did you say
你说什么
Come out, Negatone!
出来吧 负向音调!
ah
啊
Stop that
别跑
It's embarrassing
太丢脸了
Yeah ah..
呀啊..
Negatone
负向音调
Let everyone brings the smiles
让大家恢复笑脸的
the Healing Chest
治愈音樂盒
Absolute you're not getting it!!
绝对不交给你们!!
Dodo
Rere
Lala
Let's Play! Precure  Modulation!
弹奏吧!光之美少女 转调!
Strumming the wild rhythm
指尖弹奏地是狂野的曲调
Cure Melody!
旋律天使!
Strumming the tranquil melody
指尖弹奏地是柔和的曲调
Cure Rhythm!
节奏天使!
Strumming the beat's soul
指尖弹出地是灵魂的曲调
Cure Beat!
节拍天使!
Resonate! Three adult of musical suite!
传送吧! 三人的组曲!
Suite Precure?
组曲光之美少女?
Suite
Precure
What..
什么..
What's going on?
这是什么?
Negatone Test
负向音调 考试
The next question
接下来的问题
give me answer
给我回答
ah!
啊!
It talked normally
竟然它正常的讲话了
Test!?
考试!?
That the test
说是考试
More like a quiz show
但怎看都像是抢答大赛啊
Question for Cure Rhythm
向节奏天使提问
"Shiro" in English is?
"白色"用英语怎么说?
White!
Correct!
正确!
Question for Cure Beat
向节拍天使提问
"Ao" in English is?
"蓝色"用英语怎么说?
Blue!
Correct!
正是如此!
What is it doing
那家伙在做什么啊
I don't know
谁知道啊
Question for Cure Melody
向旋律天使提问
"Pink" in Japanese is?
"Pink"用日文怎么说?
Pink!
Uh
啊
Use japanese?
用日语?
Boo!
咘!
You need to study more!
再加把劲吧!
Oh ah
哦啊
Oh
啊
Original
原来
there's a rule like that
是这样的规则啊
What an annoying fellow
真是个烦人的家伙
That's not your call out
那不是你叫出来的
Negatone
负向音调嘛
That last question goes to you
刚才那一问的回答是
Bad!? Rhythm!
不好的!? 节奏天使!
Momoiro!
桃红色!
Correct!
精彩!
To Cure Beat..
向节拍天使..
That's enough!
够了!
That's two girl don't control
那两个丫头就别管了
Give Cure Melody a question
快向旋律天使提问
All right!
明白!
Melody
旋律天使
Do your best, Meow
加油 喵
Okay
嗯
Do you know how to count in English?
数数用英文怎么说?
Uh..
呃..
U..Uh...
呃..呃...
I don't know!
不知道!
ah~
啊~
ah~~
啊~~
ah~~~
啊~~~
What's 1,000?
1千怎么说?
10,000?
1万呢?
100,000,000?
1亿呢?
I don't know
不知道
I don't know!
不知道!
I don't know!!
不知道!!
It is a too pity
真是可惜
ah~ah~~
啊~啊~~
Melody
旋律天使
Ah ha ha
啊哈哈
What an idiot!
完全答不出来啊!
Because
因为
I really don't know
我真的不知道嘛
But
但是
For next time
到下次之前
I'll study hard
会学习的
I won't betray them
我不想背叛
for the sake of everyone cheering me on
鼓励过我的大家
For the sake of everybody's smiles
为了让大家展露笑容
Next
下一次
I'll try my best
我会努力
answer was absolutely out of
绝对答得出来
That's
那就是
I now
现在的我
the answer can be made
所能作出的回答
How's that an answer
这种话也能算回答吗
It is
是的
W..What?
怎..怎么了?
Whoever
无论是谁
has things they don't know
都有不了解的知识
But
但是
That's why
正是因为如此
In order to understand it will be ,we work hard
才会为了了解它而去努力
That's the important thing
这份心意是十分重要的
Cure Melody
旋律天使
Your answer
妳的回答
is correct in my heart
对我来说是优秀的喔
Crescendo Tone
克雷仙多音调
Come on
那么
now's lend to you
现在该给妳
the new my power of the time
新的力量的时刻了
Wave your hand across the keyboard
挥动妳手上的琴键吧
ah
啊
Like this?
像这样?
ah!
啊!
What amazing power..
好强大的力量..
ah!!
啊!!
Melody
旋律天使
ah
啊
It disappeared
消失了
Yes
很好
I don't know what just happened
虽然不是很明白
but here's our chance
正是攻击的好时机
但现在
The Healing Chest now
趁现在把治愈音樂盒
take it over
抢过来
Nega
Give me wait up
给我等一下
W..What?
什..什么?
If you want the Healing Chest
想要治愈音樂盒的话
then you must take our questions
就必须把我们的问题
have to answer
给回答喔
Huh?
啊?
But it's unfair
不然不公平嘛
if we don't get to ask questions
就你们那么轻松
All right
好
We'll answer your questions
那我们就接受提问
Come on
来吧
Melody
旋律天使
Let's go
要上啰
Oh
嗯
ah!
嗯!
So
那么
"Time for the Precure Quiz"
"光之美少女机智问答"
Viewers around the TV
电视机前的大家
let's think through these together!
也试着一起思考吧!
The attacks coming right now
现在我们将要使出的绝招
What are the names
名字是什么
What?
什么?
Miracle Belltier
奇迹指挥棒
Fantastic Belltier
幻想指挥棒
Love Guitar Rod
爱情吉他杖
Well then
那么
it's time
接下来
for the answer
答案揭晓啰
Come out! Tone Ring
飞翔吧!合声的高音谱光环
Precure
光之美少女
Heartful Beat Rock
心灵摇滚曲
Precure
光之美少女
Music Rondo
音乐圆舞曲
Precure
光之美少女
Music Rondo
音乐圆舞曲
Wow
哇
That's not fair
真狡猾
Meou
Not fair at all!
真狡猾!
3/4 Beat! 1, 2, 3
3拍子! 1 2 3
Finale!
终曲!
Ya doo
呀多
Mi miles
眯哩
Etc. etc
等等 等等
Poof meow poof meow!
喵噗 喵噗!
Give here
给
Mimi
Wow
哇
The Melody of Happiness
幸福的旋律
We'll finish any time now, Meow
很快就能完成了喵
What a pity
真可惜
Not the attack names
那不是绝招的名字
you told us the item names
而是我们使用的道具名
Hey
哎
Next time
下一次
We'll definitely
我们一定会
Perfectly correct answer defeat you
完美地回答正确的
That's not right
你弄错了吧
Overall
总而言之
Remember us run away, bye
给我们记住
Rare
难得
Crescendo Tone was willing to lend me her power
克雷仙多音调帮了我
but I couldn't accept it..
还是没能回报她..
Work hard for the next time
下一次努力
Just not on the line, Meow
不就行了喵
Yep
是呀
there will be a next time
还有下一次呢
Next time
下一次
I'm absolute
绝对
you'll do it
会努力的对吧
Of course
那是当然
All right
好
Next time
下一次
I'll absolute!
绝对!
Crescendo Tone's power help
不辜负克雷仙多音调的帮助
accept return to her
并回报给她
Oh!
喔!
Ding Dong nanairo neiro kirei
Ding Dong The prism of notes make a beautiful
叮 咚 七彩音色多么美丽
#kibou rainbow#
#rainbow of hope#
#希望的彩虹#
Makenai! Kokoro ni hibikiau!
The orchestra that connects your hearts is invincible!
不会输! 在心中交响!
orchestra Precure?
管弦乐 光之美少女?
Akiramecha Song! Song! Song!
When you feel worn down, song! song! song!
不能放弃 歌曲! 歌曲! 歌曲!
Kikoeru desho?
you hear that,right?
听得见吧?
Pizzicato de hazumu kimochi
And it wistfully plays your feelings to you
用手指拨奏的心情
Hora, kyoumi Sing! Sing!
So get caught up and sing, sing!
来吧兴味盎然地 歌唱! 歌唱!
namida Pianissimo
Your tears won't seem so bad
眼泪轻轻弹奏
Egao Legato!
And we'll keep on smiling together!
用笑脸来连奏!
Hitori de wa narasenai
This song can't be played alone
只靠一个人 无法奏响
Genki no onpu tomo ni Riff shitara
But if we can find a riff of happy notes
一起重复演奏 精神百倍的音符
Ooiri manin de shirazu ni kokoro
Then the cheering crowd would help make our hearts
满座的观众 让心不知不觉变得
Sharp Sharp Sharp
Maemuite
So just look ahead
朝着前方 (微笑! 组曲 光之美少女?)
(Smile! Suite Precure?)
Arukidasou
Keep on moving on
迈出步伐 (跳越! 组曲 光之美少女?)
(Skip! Suite Precure?)
Kujikenai sono hitomi ni ai yadoru idol☆
In these resolute eyes lies a loving idol☆
爱映照在无畏的眼睛里  偶像☆
Ding Dong nanairo neiro hikaru
Ding Dong The prism of notes shines
叮 咚 七彩音色闪耀光芒
#kibourainbow#
#rainbow of hope#
#希望的彩虹#
Zettai!Asu mo waratteru!
And I know when tomorrow comes to laughing!
绝对! 明天也 一定要微笑着!
Minna issho ni!
And we'll all together!
和大家一起!
Sora miage
So hold your head high
抬头望向天空(朋友! 组曲光之美少女?)
(Friends! SuitePrecure?)
Te wo tsunagou
Walk hand in hand
一起手牵手 (队伍! 组曲光之美少女?)
(Team! SuitePrecure?)
I Note (Ai no Oto) wo kanadeai
If we play that I (Note of love) together
合奏起i音符（爱之音）
Kiai! Waki ai↑ ai↑
We'll be charged with peace and love↑love↑
步调! 和睦 爱↑爱↑
Ding Dong nanairo neiro kirei
Ding Dong The prism of notes make a beautiful
叮 咚 七彩音色多么美丽
#kibourainbow#
#rainbow of hope#
#希望的彩虹#
Makenai! Kokoro ni hibikiau!
The orchestra that connects your heart is invincible!
不会输! 在心中交响!
orchestra Precure?
Orchestra Precure?
管弦乐 光之美少女?
Everyone
大家
we're training in the mountains, Meow!
一起去山间特训喵!
First up is
首先是
stamina training with karate!
用空手道锻炼身体!
Next is
接下来是
aerobics!
有氧运动!
Finally
最后
we'll with everyone singing!
大家一起唱歌!
Come on, karate
吶吶 空手道
aerobics one two
有氧运动 一 二
and sing Do Re Mi
歌唱 Do Re Mi
Really happy, Meow
真是开心呢喵
Hey!
哎哎!
That's not right, Meow
完全不对啊喵
组曲光之美少女31话(9.18播出)
To just now up
到刚才为止
we're supposed to be training, Meow
都说是特训了喵
Suite Precure?
组曲光之美少女?
One Two! Power Up in Precure Camp Meow!
力量提升在光之美少女宿营喵!
31话
一 二 !
Our harmony will resonate in your hearts!
让心中响起 合声的力量吧!
预告部分字词采用英中双字幕
本预告字幕仅供个人试看使用
若你喜欢本小队作品 请支持购买正版
中文预告翻译:svizzera
预告网页翻译:小雷
校对修订:帝台春 asdfe0
若有疑问请上光之美少女动漫论坛
prcsub.17heha.com 询问
英文字幕:采用Doremi Fansubs、CureComSubs字幕组字幕
英文翻译:Ladholyman
下集待续